[
  {
    "question": "How is the number 9 represented as a binary number?",
    "right_answer": "1001",
    "answers": [
      "1000",
      "1110",
      "1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.",
    "right_answer": "False",
    "answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What prime number comes next after 19?",
    "right_answer": "23",
    "answers": [
      "25",
      "21",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the symbol for Displacement?",
    "right_answer": "Î”r",
    "answers": [
      "dr",
      "Dp",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.",
    "right_answer": "False",
    "answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The metric prefix &quot;atto-&quot; makes a measurement how much smaller than the base unit?",
    "right_answer": "One Quintillionth",
    "answers": [
      "One Billionth",
      "One Quadrillionth",
      "One Septillionth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
    "right_answer": "True",
    "answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
    "right_answer": "False",
    "answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a trapezium have?",
    "right_answer": "4",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.",
    "right_answer": "True",
    "answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  }
]